var questions = [
    { letter: "a", answer: "apple", status: 0, question: "With the letter A:\n An ________ a day keeps the doctor away."},
    { letter: "b", answer: "banana", status: 0, question: "With the letter B:\n A long yellow fruit"},
    { letter: "c", answer: "cat", status: 0, question: "With the letter C:\n This animal makes the 'meow' sound."},
    { letter: "d", answer: "dog", status: 0, question: "With the letter D:\n This animal makes the 'woof' sound"},
    { letter: "e", answer: "eggs", status: 0, question: "With the letter E:\n Birds lay these."},
    { letter: "f", answer: "four", status: 0, question: "With the letter F:\n Eleven minus Seven (in words)"},
    { letter: "g", answer: "green", status: 0, question: "With the letter G:\n The colour of grass."},
    { letter: "h", answer: "hat", status: 0, question: "With the letter H:\n You wear this in your head."},
    { letter: "i", answer: "ink", status: 0, question: "With the letter I:\n What is the liquid inside pen."},
    { letter: "j", answer: "july", status: 0, question: "With the letter J:\n The seventh month of the year."},
    { letter: "k", answer: "kangaroo", status: 0, question: "With the letter K:\n This animal carry its baby in a pouch."},
    { letter: "l", answer: "light", status: 0, question: "With the letter L:\n The opposite of dark."},
    { letter: "m", answer: "mango", status: 0, question: "With the letter M:\n This fruit is know as the King of fruits."},
    { letter: "n", answer: "nail", status: 0, question: "With the letter N:\n Something you hit with a Hammer."},
    { letter: "o", answer: "octagon", status: 0, question: "With the letter O: \n I am a shape with 8 sides."},
    { letter: "p", answer: "peacock", status: 0, question: "With the letter P:\n National bird of India."},
    { letter: "q", answer: "quick", status: 0, question: "With the letter Q:\n Another word for fast."},
    { letter: "r", answer: "rough", status: 0, question: "With the letter R:\n The opposite of smooth."},
    { letter: "s", answer: "sun", status: 0, question: "With the letter S:\n This is the biggest thing in our solar system."},
    { letter: "t", answer: "tringle", status: 0, question: "With the letter T:\n This is a three sided shape."},
    { letter: "u", answer: "umbrella", status: 0, question: "With the letter U:\n This keep us dry during rain."},
    { letter: "v", answer: "volcano", status: 0, question: "With the letter V:\n A moutain from which lava erupts."},
    { letter: "w", answer: "west", status: 0, question: "With the letter W:\n North, south, east, _______."},
    { letter: "x", answer: "xray", status: 0, question: "Contains the letter X:\n A picture that shows your bones."},
    { letter: "y", answer: "yell", status: 0, question: "With the letter Y:\n Another word for shout (4 letter)."},
    { letter: "z", answer: "zebra", status: 0, question: "With the letter Z:\n I am an animal with black and white strips."},]

var questions2 = [
  { letter: "a", answer: "apple", status: 0, question: "With the letter A:\n An ________ a day keeps the doctor away."},
    { letter: "b", answer: "banana", status: 0, question: "With the letter B:\n A long yellow fruit"},
    { letter: "c", answer: "cat", status: 0, question: "With the letter C:\n This animal makes the 'meow' sound."},
    { letter: "d", answer: "dog", status: 0, question: "With the letter D:\n This animal makes the 'woof' sound"},
    { letter: "e", answer: "eggs", status: 0, question: "With the letter E:\n Birds lay these."},
    { letter: "f", answer: "four", status: 0, question: "With the letter F:\n Eleven minus Seven (in words)"},
    { letter: "g", answer: "green", status: 0, question: "With the letter G:\n The colour of grass."},
    { letter: "h", answer: "hat", status: 0, question: "With the letter H:\n You wear this in your head."},
    { letter: "i", answer: "ink", status: 0, question: "With the letter I:\n What is the liquid inside pen."},
    { letter: "j", answer: "july", status: 0, question: "With the letter J:\n The seventh month of the year."},
    { letter: "k", answer: "kangaroo", status: 0, question: "With the letter K:\n This animal carry its baby in a pouch."},
    { letter: "l", answer: "light", status: 0, question: "With the letter L:\n The opposite of dark."},
    { letter: "m", answer: "mango", status: 0, question: "With the letter M:\n This fruit is know as the King of fruits."},
    { letter: "n", answer: "nail", status: 0, question: "With the letter N:\n Something you hit with a Hammer."},
    { letter: "o", answer: "octagon", status: 0, question: "With the letter O: \n I am a shape with 8 sides."},
    { letter: "p", answer: "peacock", status: 0, question: "With the letter P:\n National bird of India."},
    { letter: "q", answer: "quick", status: 0, question: "With the letter Q:\n Another word for fast."},
    { letter: "r", answer: "rough", status: 0, question: "With the letter R:\n The opposite of smooth."},
    { letter: "s", answer: "sun", status: 0, question: "With the letter S:\n This is the biggest thing in our solar system."},
    { letter: "t", answer: "tringle", status: 0, question: "With the letter T:\n This is a three sided shape."},
    { letter: "u", answer: "umbrella", status: 0, question: "With the letter U:\n This keep us dry during rain."},
    { letter: "v", answer: "volcano", status: 0, question: "With the letter V:\n A moutain from which lava erupts."},
    { letter: "w", answer: "west", status: 0, question: "With the letter W:\n North, south, east, _______."},
    { letter: "x", answer: "xray", status: 0, question: "Contains the letter X:\n A picture that shows your bones."},
    { letter: "y", answer: "yell", status: 0, question: "With the letter Y:\n Another word for shout (4 letter)."},
    { letter: "z", answer: "zebra", status: 0, question: "With the letter Z:\n I am an animal with black and white strips."},]


var questions3 = [
  { letter: "a", answer: "apple", status: 0, question: "With the letter A:\n An ________ a day keeps the doctor away."},
  { letter: "b", answer: "banana", status: 0, question: "With the letter B:\n A long yellow fruit"},
  { letter: "c", answer: "cat", status: 0, question: "With the letter C:\n This animal makes the 'meow' sound."},
  { letter: "d", answer: "dog", status: 0, question: "With the letter D:\n This animal makes the 'woof' sound"},
  { letter: "e", answer: "eggs", status: 0, question: "With the letter E:\n Birds lay these."},
  { letter: "f", answer: "four", status: 0, question: "With the letter F:\n Eleven minus Seven (in words)"},
  { letter: "g", answer: "green", status: 0, question: "With the letter G:\n The colour of grass."},
  { letter: "h", answer: "hat", status: 0, question: "With the letter H:\n You wear this in your head."},
  { letter: "i", answer: "ink", status: 0, question: "With the letter I:\n What is the liquid inside pen."},
  { letter: "j", answer: "july", status: 0, question: "With the letter J:\n The seventh month of the year."},
  { letter: "k", answer: "kangaroo", status: 0, question: "With the letter K:\n This animal carry its baby in a pouch."},
  { letter: "l", answer: "light", status: 0, question: "With the letter L:\n The opposite of dark."},
  { letter: "m", answer: "mango", status: 0, question: "With the letter M:\n This fruit is know as the King of fruits."},
  { letter: "n", answer: "nail", status: 0, question: "With the letter N:\n Something you hit with a Hammer."},
  { letter: "o", answer: "octagon", status: 0, question: "With the letter O: \n I am a shape with 8 sides."},
  { letter: "p", answer: "peacock", status: 0, question: "With the letter P:\n National bird of India."},
  { letter: "q", answer: "quick", status: 0, question: "With the letter Q:\n Another word for fast."},
  { letter: "r", answer: "rough", status: 0, question: "With the letter R:\n The opposite of smooth."},
  { letter: "s", answer: "sun", status: 0, question: "With the letter S:\n This is the biggest thing in our solar system."},
  { letter: "t", answer: "tringle", status: 0, question: "With the letter T:\n This is a three sided shape."},
  { letter: "u", answer: "umbrella", status: 0, question: "With the letter U:\n This keep us dry during rain."},
  { letter: "v", answer: "volcano", status: 0, question: "With the letter V:\n A moutain from which lava erupts."},
  { letter: "w", answer: "west", status: 0, question: "With the letter W:\n North, south, east, _______."},
  { letter: "x", answer: "xray", status: 0, question: "Contains the letter X:\n A picture that shows your bones."},
  { letter: "y", answer: "yell", status: 0, question: "With the letter Y:\n Another word for shout (4 letter)."},
  { letter: "z", answer: "zebra", status: 0, question: "With the letter Z:\n I am an animal with black and white strips."},]


let randomQuestions = [];

function getRandomArray(i) {
  let allQuestions = [questions,questions2,questions3];
  let index = Math.floor(Math.random() * 3);
  return allQuestions[index][i];
}

function setRandomArray() {
  for(let i = 0; i < 26; i++) {
    randomQuestions.push(getRandomArray(i));
  }
}